AVNEET SINGH SANDHU 403-590-1987

avneet2542@gmail.com

Summary

Reliable, energetic, and dedicated customer service representative with previous experience in resolving intricate customer enquiries. Passionate and goes above and beyond in each interaction with clients to provide the highest quality services possible. Extremely committed, driven, and motivated to constantly improve job performance.

Work Experience

Cashier at shell gas station (Winnipeg)

July 2019 – March 2022

- Address customer concerns in a timely fashion regarding products and promotions to ensure customer satisfaction
- Direct delivery scheduling and stock supplies in coordination with external personnel
- Maintain daily record of sales and process payments
- Organize various tasks such as cleanliness, stocking, processing payments receiving deliveries at a busy gas station

Security Guard at Black Bird Security (Winnipeg) Aug 2021 – Mar 2022

- To monitor for vandalism or theft and take appropriate action
- Alert the authorities about an incident
- Take lead on dealing with any problems while keeping the best interest of the clients in mind

Taxi driver (Winnipeg)

Dec 2020 – April 2021

- Pick up and drop off customers on request
- Ensure a comfortable ride for customers by providing a clean and well-maintained vehicle

- Help customers to load and unload the luggage
- Be punctual, reliable, and excellent at time management
- Ensure customer satisfaction by being considerate about special requests specially for customers with kids and special needs
- Ensure safety of customers while driving

Customer care executive in Teleperformance

Jan 2019 – March 2019

- Demonstrated problem solving through providing technical support
- Worked under pressure to find time bound and effective solutions
- Demonstrated excellent communication skills while working remotely over the phone

Education

Postgraduate (International business Management) Manitoba institute of Trades and Technology, Winnipeg, MB	2019 – 2020
Master of Science (Computer Science) Guru Nanak Dev University, Amritsar, India	2015 – 2017
Bachelor of Computer Application. Guru Nanak Dev University, Amritsar, India	2012- 2015

Skills Summary

- Excellent communication skills
- Record of accident-free driving
- Safety minded
- Quick learner
- Knowledge about technology-based navigation
- Reliable and hard worker
- Positive and friendly attitude
- Motivated team player
- Detail oriented
- Good at time management

Class 5 Full (Winnipeg, MB)

• References available on request